Stop trying to be like all those other girls you see
You're better off just being yourself
If you can feel the spark in your heart,
come search for your ideals
Every single memory we've made,
we'll snap'em in half
and complete the set with our friends!
Make it! Once you get started, you're invicible!
Make up! Headed towards a radiant future
Making Drama, switch on!
Anyone can be anything!
You can dancE!
You can walk the runway!
Sing a song!
Let's make a miracle!
Cyalume Change!
Make up! Giving up on that dream is just not in the cards!
Make it! Once you get started, you're invicible!
Make up! Headed towards a radiant future
Your dream's not just a dream anymore
Anyone can be anything!
PriPara PriPara-dise